Jeremy Tuesley

Technologies: React, Javascript, Node.js, Typescript, Ruby, Ruby on Rails, GraphQL, Git, HTML, CSS

Email: jeremytuesley@gmail.com

Mobile: 0402 305 040

Portfolio:

https://www.jeremytuesley.com/ LinkedIn: @jeremy-tuesley

GitHub:

https://github.com/jeremytuesley/

A dedicated, objective-driven developer, who after 6 years in administrative warehousing, decided on a career change into tech to pursue his true interests, starting with a bootcamp and self-study. I have a strong passion for learning, helping others in need and strive to deliver my best wherever I go. While I have a front-end bias, I welcome any opportunities to learn and further expand my skill set.

Experience

Freelance Developer LinkedIn

Jan 2021 - Present

- Side projects, XLExtends maintenance and on request additions
- Leetcodes and assisting new learners via discord communities

SignHow (RoR) Website Link - Mobile View

Contract Full-stack Developer (Ruby on Rails)

June 2022 - August 2023

- Developing pages based off Figma wireframes & creating reusable components
- Daily stand-ups/ progress reports
- Created reusable components and the API documentation to use them.
- Adjusted pre-existing pages to the MVC structure, refactoring into ERB.

Projects - More shown on Github & Portfolio

XLExtends (Commercial) Website Link - GitHub Repository Link

July 2021 - May 2022

Front End Developer (MERN)

- Designed and developed MERN stack shopfront website, with a booking, and payment system.
- Worked in a 3 person team, with my role managing sprints, developing the front-end side of the website using React, writing integration/ unit tests with Cypress, achieving 90%+ features tested.
- Managing sprints consisted of writing all user stories and then applying priority, estimated time taken and then
 assigning them to a sprint and developer.

PC-Mart Website Link - GitHub Repository Link

May 2021

Two-sided Marketplace Web App (Ruby on Rails)

- Made this project because there's no real marketplace for used computer parts
- Full stack marketplace web application was built with Ruby on Rails for front-end and backend
- Currently has 15+ registered users, with a history of 30+ listings
- User authentication handled with Devise

Education

Academy of Information Technology

Diploma of Information Technology
Full-stack software engineer bootcamp program

Feb 2021 - Aug 2021 Graduated

Tafe Queensland

Certificate IV in ATP (STEM)

Electives: Physics, Pure Maths, Academic Learning

Feb 2017 Completed with Honours